

ABHILASHA PANCHAL

SUMMARY

Born and raised in Mumbai city, India. Experienced Mandarin Language Trainer and worked in the Paper Industry as a Sales Relationship Manager and Export Sales. Skilled in Communication, Easily Adaptable, and Creativity skills. Volunteered at an NGO. Strong Education professional with a Mandarin language course from Zhejiang University and Bachelor's degree in Commerce and Advance Diploma in International Business from Mumbai University.

PERSONAL INFO



Mumbai, India - 400083



+91 9967344914



abhilashapanchal@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/abhilashapanchal/

EXPERIENCE

Coniferous Multitrade Pvt Ltd

Sales Relationship Manager and Export Sales January, 2021- Present

- Handling Export Sales
- Managing Suppliers
- Lead Generation
- Managing Customer Relations

Freelancing

Mandarin Language Trainer February, 2019- Present

 Certified Mandarin language trainer and teaching HSK 1-3 as a freelancer with experience in teaching age groups of 7-60 year olds.

EDUCATION

IELTS Examination

Band 6.5 November 2022

<u>Oscar Academy</u>

Advance Diploma in International Business June 2021- January 2022

Zhejiang University, China

Mandarin Language Course September 2019- January 2020

HSK Examination

- Cleared HSK 2 with 180/200 in July 2018
- Cleared HSK 3 with 198/300 in April 2019

KJ Somaiya Sci and Comm.

Bachelor's Degree in Commerce. 2016-2018

LANGUAGES







ENGLISH

HINDI

MANDARIN





GUJARATI

MARATHI

INTEREST

- Exploring New Cuisines
- Traveling
- Trekking
- Learning about different cultures

SKILLS

- Communication Skills
- Team Work
- Willingness to Learn
- Resilience
- Self Management
- Goal oriented
- Ambitious

OTHER INFO

- Date of Birth- 1997/04/01
- Marital Status- Single